# First Last Full-Stack Developer

Full-Stack Developer with five years of experience leading both front-end and back-end development, and performing quality assurance. Led teams of 5-15 people across technology, business, and design departments.

San Francisco, CA 12345 +1 234 567-890 first.last@resumeworded.com linkedin.com/in/resumeworded

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Resume Worded, New York, NY Full-Stack Developer

#### January 2020 - Present

- Trained and supported 10 new hires remotely to conduct interviews, lead lectures, and debug code through the 2020 Advanced Immersive Program which focused on teaching software engineering and core web technologies.
- Ensured compatibility with major browsers on mobile and desktop
  platforms by coordinating core server product development in Spring MVC
  and Spring SOA service components for more than 50 client sites.
- Improved performance by resolving more than 80 critical bugs in the company's products to improve performance.

# Growthsi, Remote

# Web Developer

## July 2016 - January 2020

- Developed a brand new administration panel for purchasing agent business, which increased the customer service by 90% and improved the efficiency of operating by over 25%.
- Increased customer satisfaction to 85% by creating databases utilizing PHP5, PDO, and MySQL that streamlined trucking operations from creating, assigning, and tracking truckloads.
- Developed 25 original e-commerce website and web applications, encompassing design, coding, testing, and maintenance whilst supervising a team of 15 web developers.

# Resume Worded, Boston, MA

## IT Analyst

#### January 2012 - June 2016

- Achieved annual cost savings of over \$170,000 by partnering with the enterprise's procurement contract management system, service level agreements, policies, and procedures.
- Reduced help desk tickets by 80% and recovering at least 35% of profits
  annually by developing a value-stream map of project delivery lifecycle and
  analyzing the delays and wait time of delivering a function to customer.

#### **SKILLS**

Blackboard Software Apache Ant Microsoft PowerShell ABAP UNIX Shell GoogleAngularJS JQuery MYSQL

#### **EDUCATION**

# Resume Worded University

Master of Software Engineering January 2012

New York, NY

- Awards: Resume Worded Teaching Fellow (only 5 awarded to class), Dean's List 2012 (Top 10%)
- Completed one-year study abroad with Singapore University

#### OTHER

- Volunteer 20 hours/month at the ABC foundation, leading pro-bono city projects
- Advanced Immersive Program (2020)